leaf5 = [
{"question":"暴風","Answer":"bàofēng"},
{"question":"電筒","Answer":"diàntǒng"},
{"question":"沾","Answer":"zhān"},
{"question":"泥土","Answer":"nítǔ"},
{"question":"梯子","Answer":"tīzi"},
{"question":"抹","Answer":"mǒ"},
{"question":"顏料","Answer":"yánliào"},
{"question":"調色盤","Answer":"diàosèpán"},
{"question":"零散","Answer":"língsǎn"},
{"question":"擺放","Answer":"bǎifàng"},
{"question":"恍然大悟","Answer":"huǎngrándàwù"},
{"question":"窗","Answer":"chuāng"},
{"question":"受盡","Answer":"shòujìn"},
{"question":"淋","Answer":"lín"},
{"question":"貝阿蒙","Answer":"bèi āméng"},
{"question":"掉落","Answer":"diàoluò"},
{"question":"爬","Answer":"pá"},
{"question":"磚牆","Answer":"zhuānqiáng"},
{"question":"梯子","Answer":"tīzi"}
]